deltacommunitycu.com 2012-05-05

# FACTS

                                                                                                                            Rev. 1/12
                                       Privacy and Opt-Out Notification
                                                     What does Delta Community Credit Union
      FACTS                                              do with your personal information?
                               Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                               consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
Why?                           how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully
                               to understand what we do.
                               The types of information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with
                               us. This information can include:
What?                               • Social Security Number and Credit Score
                                    • Income and Employment Information
                                    • Purchase History and Payment History
                               All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday
                               business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’
How?                           personal information, the reasons Delta Community Credit Union chooses to share, and
                               whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                             Does Delta Community          Can you limit this
Reasons we can share your personal information
                                                                               Credit Union share?              sharing?
For our everyday business purposes-
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s),
respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to                        YES                         NO
credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes-
to offer our products and services to you                                             YES                        YES
For joint marketing with other financial companies                                    YES                        YES
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes-
information about your transactions and experiences                                   YES                         NO
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes-
Information about your creditworthiness                                               YES                        YES
For our affiliates to market to you                                                   YES                        YES
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                    YES                        YES
                                        • Call 1-800-544-3328 or 404-715-4725 or
                                        • Visit us online: www.DeltaCommunityCU.com
To limit                           Please note:
our sharing                        If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date
                                   we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we can continue to share your
                                   information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit
                                   our sharing.
Questions?                         Call 1-800-544-3328 or go to www.DeltaCommunityCU.com

Page 2
What we do
How does Delta Community Credit Union protect my        To protect your personal information from unauthorized
personal information?                                   access and use, we use security measures that comply with
                                                        federal law. These measures include computer safeguards
                                                        and secured files and buildings.
How does Delta Community Credit Union collect my        We collect your personal information, for example, when you
personal information?                                        • Open an Account
                                                             • Apply for a Loan
                                                             • Give us your Contact Information
                                                        We also collect your nonpublic personal information from
                                                        others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?                          Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                             • sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes-
                                                               information about your creditworthiness
                                                             • affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                             • sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold
                                                        Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
jointly with someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                                              Companies related by common ownership or control. They
                                                        can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                             • Our affiliates include financial companies such as
                                                                Members Insurance Advisors.
Nonaffiliates                                           Companies not related by common ownership or control.
                                                        They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                             • Nonaffiliates we share with can include insurance
                                                                companies, service providers and other financial
                                                                institutions.
Joint Marketing                                         A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial
                                                        companies that together market financial products or
                                                        services to you.
                                                             • Our joint marketing partners include insurance
                                                                companies and service providers.
